http://www.pinktentacle.com/privacy-policy/

Art/CultureSci/TechArchivesTagsRSS
Privacy Policy
04 Jul 2006
This site (www.pinktentacle.com) respects the privacy and rights of its visitors and maintains a strict "no spam" policy. No effort is made to identify individuals without their knowledge, and no information you volunteer (name, email address, etc.) will ever willingly be provided to a third party.
This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by this site and how it is used.
- Log Files (StatCounter and Google Analytics)
Like many other websites, this site makes use of log files (including StatCounter and Google Analytics) for the purpose of analyzing trends, administering the site, and understanding how visitors interact with the site. Visitor information in the log files includes, but is not limited to, internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks. Data is collected anonymously without identifying individual users, and none of this data is linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Both StatCounter and Google Analytics use their own cookies to track visitor interactions.
According to Google Analytics Terms of Service, the information generated by Google's cookie about your use of this site will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google may transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
- DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party vendor, also uses the DART cookie to serve ads to you on this site, based on your visit to this site and other Internet sites displaying Google Adsense ads. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
This site has no access to or control over how Google uses this cookie.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. Some browsers will indicate when a cookie is being sent and allow you to decline cookies on a case-by-case basis. You can find more detailed information about how to manage cookies at the website for your particular browser.
If you require additional information or have any questions about the privacy policy of this website, please feel free to contact: edo [at] pinktentacle [dot] com.
Comments Off on Privacy Policy
No Comments
Comments are closed.
Mail mail [@] pinktentacle.com
Copyright © Pink Tentacle - Some Rights Reserved (Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial 3.0 License)
Powered by WordPress - Privacy Policy - RSS
